ANTONELLA SCARIN

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | BRAND DEVELOPER

3180 Mt. Seymour Parkway, Lower floor, North Vancuover, BC, V7H 1G3

(778) 886-4235

antonella.scarin.l@gmail.com

(in) linkedin.com/in/antonellascarin

My past studies and my experience working in a creative studio have given me the necessary tools to become a professional in the creative business. Now, I am ready to take the next step in my professional career and consolidate it on the west coast of Canada. I am very organized, a planner, a fast learner and a natural leader capable of making a positive contribution.

EDUCATION

Universidad Peruana de Ciencias Aplicadas Lima, Perú

2012 - 2016

- Bachelor in Graphic Design
- Top 25 percent

Peruano Alemán Max Uhle School Arequipa, Perú

2010 - 2011

■ IBO (International Baccalaureate Organization)

WORK EXPERIENCE

ByAntonella (Freelance work)

Owner May 2015 – Current

Execute and plan budgets that fit the needs of my clients while generating a work plan that contains research, conceptualization, and development of the brand image and the brand manual.

- Carry out around 30 projects in the last two years, that cover areas such as branding, packaging, magazines, web
 design and others.
- Work on several projects for entrepreneurs, which included the development of naming, conceptualization, brand identity and branding stages.

Maan Digital Lab

Co-founder and creative director

October 2020 - Current

- Co-founder of a digital laboratory focused on helping new businesses to enhance their brands in the digital world.
- Propose, plan and execute digital campaigns and strategies that meet the goals of each client.
- Within the first 8 months of working with our clients, we have helped them reach 1000 followers.
- In 2021, we managed to obtain up to 10 accounts currently active within our first year of work.
- Create solid and trusting relationships with our clients with the purpose of having an effective work environment with each of them.
- Supervision and creative direction for the graphics developed for social media, branding and web design.

Kids on Wheels

Marketing coordinator and Lead instructor

May 2022 - September 2022

- Rebrand the Kids on Wheel logo and assets by generating a new "brand universe" with valuable resources, graphics and a brand manual for the proper use of the brand.
- Advertised the program through marketing strategies, web content and social media marketing.
- Scheduled and coordinated all the Kids on Wheels sessions with the different community centres and daycares.
- Created, organized and delivered a training program for the instructors. Led balance bike camps with a group of instructors, ensuring they perform their tasks properly and promptly.
- Designed and published different social media posts with the purpose of advertising the camps, gaining more followers, and having more presence in the digital world.

Mt. Seymour Resorts Ltd.

Retail Lead Supervisor and e-commerce assistant

November 2021 – April 2022

- Completed and checked monthly inventory counts and store equipment checks with RSM.
- Provided training to staff members regarding product knowledge, customer service and mountain information.
- Supervised staff in maintaining overall cleanliness and safety of the stores.
- Monitored, checked and fixed daily cashouts.
- Provided Retail cashiers with all tools and assistance needed to successfully sell and complete the duties.
- Assisted in keeping an accurate and organized ShopKeep register system.
- Managed incoming orders and deliveries while keeping the website updated, graphed banners and optimized the overall look.

Provincia Creative Studio, Arequipa, Peru

Account and planning director, Graphic designer

August 2018 - March 2021

- Be the link between clients, suppliers and the creative studio while designing and controlling the creative processes within the studio and the coworkers.
- Organized the company agenda by scheduling meetings with clients and suppliers, and making sure to always be on time with deadlines.
- Responsible for communication with the accounting team, making sure that the corresponding invoices and receipts were issued, while also collecting debts from clients.
- Worked in hand with the creative director on several photoshoots around Peru.
- Participated in various design projects from different industries by developing solid storytelling and holistic branding.

VOLUNTEER AND COMMUNITY EXPERIENCE

Perú 2021 Presidential Elections

April 2020

 Volunteer in the organization of the first round of the General Elections of Peru in the polling stations in Vancouver, British Columbia.

Fibras March 2021

Digital Training Program

Mentor of two artisan women with whom I worked on emotional intelligence, so they embrace to manage their business.

SKILLS

Languages:

- Fluent in English; oral and written.
- Fluent in Spanish; oral and written.
- Intermediate German

Software:

Proficient user of:

- Windows
- MacOS
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe InDesing
- Adobe Lightroom
- Adobe Premier
- 3D Max
- Canva
- Figma

Expertise:

- Branding
- Social media
- Editorial design
- Packaging
- Web design
- Photophraphy

Courses:

- Naming course from Domestika
- Naming course from Crehana
- Impact of Packaging Design from Labasad
- Money and finance management for creatives course from Domestika
- Inbound Marketing course from Netzum
- ByFutura Creative Agency Workshop
- Preliminary English Test PET (Cambridge)
- Deutsche Sprach Diplom I and II (German)

ANTONELLA SCARIN

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | BRAND DEVELOPER

(9) 3180 Mt. Seymour Parkway, Lower floor, North Vancuover, BC, V7H 1G3

(778) 886-4235

antonella.scarin.l@gmail.com

(in) linkedin.com/in/antonellascarin

REFERENCES

1. Mike Koski

The BC Cycling Coalition Executive Director

Phone: (778) 871-9207

Email: mike.koski@bccycling.ca

2. Samantha Joy

The BC Cycling Coalition Marketing and Outreach Coordinator

Phone: (604) 787-8945

Email: samantha.joy@bccycling.ca

3. Maya Goldstein

Kids on Wheels Founder & Manager

Phone: (604) 653-4160

Email: maya.goldstein@bccycling.ca

4. Farn Mirza

Mt. Seymour Resort Retail Manager

Phone: (604) 657-4454

PORTFOLIO

https://info755099.wixsite.com/antonellaportfolio

